

DAVID BOCCALANDRO

TUTOR AT HENRY && CODERHOUSE FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFORMATION

Buenos Aires, Argentina. Cellphone: 11 3077 5454 Mail: davidboccalandro@hotmail.com



SOCIAL MEDIA

linkedin.com/in/david-boccalandrodeveloper/ github.com/DavidBoccalandro

Under development...

ABOUT ME:

I'm David, I'm 29 years old and I'm from Buenos Aires, Argentina. I love to challenge myself daily since there is always something new to learn when it comes to programming. I have experience in collections and administration, a background that currently guides me: when I reconnected with programming I noticed that I find it easy to learn quickly, be organized, communicate, and many other skills that have helped me become a good programmer and tutor.

FORMAL WORK EXPERIENCE FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Back End Tutor

Coderhouse | March 2022 - to date

- Follow-up of students and monitoring of their progress.
- Generation of greater dynamism and curiosity, sharing experiences and integrating students in the class.
- Correction of projects and challenges, query management.
- Support and post-class help. Feedback. Review of concepts.

Full Stack Teaching Assistant

Bootcamp Soy Henry | December 2021 - to date

- Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration into the study group.
- Guide them in the first steps of the course and assist in solving exercises
- Promote group collaboration (Pair Programming)
- Propose ideas to improve Bootcamp processes

WORK EXPERIENCE IN OTHER AREAS

BackOffice Analyst Sr.

Martinez de Alzaga | August 2015 - September 2021

- Adjustments, remissions, transfers, unallocated payments.
- Payment proposals and agreements,
- Free of debt, certificates, receipts, invoices, payment coupons.
- Management of mails, sms, chat, Facebook, Twitter, Whatsapp, Google.
- Control of fraudulent cases, deceased, referred to Consumer Protection or with legal complaints.
- Counter service.

Call Center Supervisor

Martinez de Alzaga | May 2015 - July 2015

- Monitoring of operators, signings, sanctions, objectives.
- Made online reports on calls.
- Customer service in a compromising situation or with excessive difficulty for the operator.

ACADEMIC TRAINING

Full Stack Web Developer

Henry Bootcamp | October 2021 - March 2022

• +800 hours of theoretical-practical coursework. Training in front-end and back-end technologies.

Programming

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional | 2011 - 2012

• Basic fundamentals of programming.

Business Administration

Universidad de Buenos Aires | 2020 - 2022

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

FoodApp - Full Stack Developer

Henry Bootcamp | January 2022 - February 2022

- The "spoonacular" API was used with the bootcamp PERN stack
- Technologies: Pure CSS, React.js, Redux, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL and Sequelize.
- Some features and components: landing, home, filters, ordering, pagination, search bar.
- Link: https://food-app-fawn.vercel.app/

JSeekers - Full Stack Developer

Henry Bootcamp | February 2022 - March 2022

- Progressive Web App for job search as a developer.
- Two types of users, online chat, filters and orders, pipeline, notifications, whatsapp, payment gateway.
- Technologies: Socket.io, AuthO, Multer, Mercadopago, Heroku, React, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Tailwind, among others.
- Link: https://pf-seekerpro.herokuapp.com/

SKILLS Hard (technologies)

- React | Redux
- Bootstrap | Sass | Tailwind
- HTML | CSS | JavaScript
- Node.js | Express
- SQL | PostgreSQL | Sequelize
- TypeScript |
- Git | GitHub
- SCRUM | Trello

- Assertive communication
- Teamwork
- Problem resolution.
- Analytical capacity.
- Adaptation to change.
- Love for challenges.



